Dorothy Kenyon Papers, 1850-1998
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES VI. ACTIVITIES AND ORGANIZATIONS (1923-1971)
  - Lower West Side Community Development Activities, [see also SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS]
    - Community Corporation of the Lower West Side
      - Predecessors
        - Lower West Side Anti-Poverty Board, Inc.
          - Miscellaneous: lists, notes, and printed material, 1965, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Planning documents: plans for elections and membership, 1966-67, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Incorporation: by-laws, minutes, guidelines, and certification of incorporation, 1967, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, 1967-71, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - Memoranda, 1967-71, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Board of Directors
        - Correspondence, 1969-71, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 6)
        - Lists, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 7)
        - Memoranda, 1967-71, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 8)
        - Minutes, 1968-71, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Committees
        - Community: correspondence and minutes, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 10)
        - Legal Advisory: publicity, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - Personnel: correspondence and minutes, 1969-71 (Box 44, Folder 12)
      - Proposals, 1967-69, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Publicity, 1966-69 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Reports, 1968-69 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous: contacts and lists, n.d. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Hudson Guild
      - General: constitution and correspondence, 1963-70 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Board of Trustees: correspondence and minutes, 1967-69 (Box 45, Folder 5)
      - Committees
        - Building: agenda, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 6)
        - Constitution revision: minutes, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 7)
        - Council: agendas and minutes, 1965-69 (Box 45, Folder 8)
        - Neighborhood Development: minutes, 1959 (Box 45, Folder 9)
        - Program Policy: minutes, 1967-68 (Box 45, Folder 10)
      - Finances, 1966-68 (Box 45, Folder 11)
      - Memoranda, 1965-70 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Programs: proposals, 1965-70 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - Farm Conferences: minutes, publicity, schedules, and recommendations, 1963-68 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Lower West Side Community Progress Center, [see Community Progress Committee] (Box 45)
    - Mobilization for Youth
      - Investigation by the City of New York: publicity, 1964-65 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      - Legal Services
        - General: assessments, proposals, newspaper clippings, correspondence, memoranda, notes, and petitions, 1965-67, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 2)
        - Advisory Board: correspondence, membership lists, memoranda, and minutes, 1967-69, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 3)
        - Board of Directors: correspondence, membership lists, memoranda, and minutes, 1967-71, n.d. (Box 46, Folder 4)
        - Cases
          - County of NY v. John DeClef, Sherman Crawford, Ross Graham, Carol Birnbaum, Martha Sells, Judith Santiago, Patricia Rosen, Carol Herman, Alberto Balora: correspondence, memoranda, notes, photos, publicity, and trial transcript, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 5)
          - Young Lords Party, et al., v New York: motion (includes Mary Kaufman), 1971 (Box 46)
      - Twenty-Third Street Association: correspondence, newsletters, and program, 1963-69, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Lower West Side Community Progress Center, [see Community Progress Committee] (Box 46)
  - Manhattan District Planning Board #4
    - Correspondence (includes Constance Baker Motley, Borough President, and A. Philip Randolph), 1963-71 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1963-69 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - McCarthy Hearings, [see also SERIES I, BIOGRAPHICAL--newspaper clippings and FBI file; SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS; SERIES IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIAL; and SERIES X. OVERSIZED MATERIAL--cartoon by Herblock]
    - Charges
      - Senate Foreign Relations Subcommittee's investigation and charges: transcript, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
      - McCarthy's statements about Dorothy Kenyon and description of exhibits: typescripts, 1950, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Defense
      - Letters and statements in support of Dorothy Kenyon, 1950, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Research and preparation
        - General: correspondence, lists, memoranda, and research notes, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 5)
        - American Committee for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom: research notes, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 6)
        - American Committee for Anti-Nazi Literature: newspaper (Box 47, Folder 7)
        - American Committee for the Protection of the Foreign Born: correspondence and printed material, 1940-41, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 8)
        - American Labor Party: correspondence and newspaper clippings, 1939-40 (Box 47, Folder 9)
        - American Lawyers Committee to American Relations with Spain: research notes, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 10)
        - American Russian Institute: research notes, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 11)
        - Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies: correspondence and newspaper clipping, 1940-41 (Box 47, Folder 12)
        - Conference on Pan American Democracy: correspondence and research notes, 1939-40, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 13)
        - Consumers Union: research notes, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 14)
        - Film Audiences for Democracy: research notes, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 15)
        - Films for Democracy: research notes, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 16)
        - Greater New York Emergency Conference on Unalienable Rights: research notes, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 17)
        - League of Women Shoppers: research notes, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 18)
        - Milk Consumers Protective Committee: research notes, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 19)
        - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship: correspondence (includes Corliss Lamont), minutes, newspaper clippings, and research notes, 1944-45, 1949-50 (Box 47, Folder 20)
        - Political Prisoners Bail Fund Committee: correspondence and research notes, 1941-50 (Box 47, Folder 21)
        - Spanish Refugee Relief Campaign: correspondence and printed material, 1939-40 (Box 47, Folder 22)
        - Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade: correspondence and research notes, 1944-50 (Box 47, Folder 23)
        - Washington Committee to Lift the Spanish Embargo: research notes, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 24)
      - Tydings Senate Foreign Relations Committee Hearings: transcript and statement (by Kenyon), 1950 (Box 47, Folder 25-26)
      - Responses and recollections by Kenyon: manuscripts and notes, 1954, 1971, n.d. (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Mideastern Cooperatives: clippings and newsletters, 1932-69 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Mobilization for Youth, [SEE Lower West Side Community Development Activities] (Box 47)
  - Modern Community Developers: correspondence 1964-67 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Narcotic Addiction Control Commission: correspondence, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People Legal Defense and Educational Fund, Inc.
    - Correspondence (includes letters to Ralph Bunche, Senator Paul Douglas, Constance Baker Motley), 1964-66 (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Cases
      - Chatmon et al. v. United States of America in U.S. Court of Appeals, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 32)
      - Strauder v. West Virginia, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Robert Swain v. Alabama, Supreme Court of the U.S., October term, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous: notes and printed material, 1957, 1964-65, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - National Association of Women Lawyers: conference programs, 1945-49 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - National Association for the Repeal of Abortion Laws: correspondence, 1969 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - National Business and Professional Council, Inc.: correspondence, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - National Businessmen's Council: correspondence, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing: correspondence, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - National Committee for Rural Schools: correspondence, n.d. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - National Committees of United Church Women: program, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews: correspondence, 1965 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - National Conference on Religion and Race: correspondence (includes Martin Luther King Jr., George Meany, A. Philip Randolph, Walter Reuther, Carl Sandburg, and Francis Cardinal Spellman), 1963 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - National Federation of Business and Professional Women's Clubs, Inc.: resolution, 1948 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - National Organization for Women: clippings, constitution, correspondence (includes Betty Friedan, Aileen Hernandez, and Ti Grace Atkinson), minutes, and press releases, 1966-71 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - National Public Affairs Committee: minutes, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - National Research Council on Peace Strategy: correspondence, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - National Student Association: program, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - National University of Ireland Club: invitation, 1964 (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - National Women's Political Caucus: correspondence, 1971 (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Negotiation NOW: clipping and telegram, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - New Chelsea Club
    - Correspondence (includes Herbert Lehman, Eleanor Roosevelt, and Robert Wagner), 1959-67 (Box 48, Folder 21-24)
    - Publicity, 1960-65 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    - Reports, 1959-60, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Speeches by Kenyon and others, 1963-65, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous: printed material, 1959-63, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - New Chelsea Reform Democratic Club
    - General: agendas, minutes, and printed material, 1966-69 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1964-71 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - New Era Club: clippings and printed material, 1950-54 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - The New School: invitations, 1963-64 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - New York Association for the Blind: press release, 1941 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - New York Business and Professional Men's and Women's Committee: correspondence (includes George McGovern), 1971 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - New York City Bar Association: correspondence, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - New York City Council Against Poverty: correspondence, minutes, and publicity, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - New York City Democratic Committee First Annual Dinner: seating list, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - New York Committee for Democratic Voters
    - Correspondence, 1961-71 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Memos, minutes, and miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Judicial Convention, 1962 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Patronage Abuses Committee, 1961-64 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - New York Conference on the Educational Park: correspondence (includes Constance Baker Motley), 1965 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - New York Council for Landmarks Preservation: newsletter, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - New York County Lawyers Association: correspondence and printed material, 1960-64 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - New York Democratic Committee: program and seating list, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  - New York Democratic State Committee: correspondence, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  - New York Department of Licenses: clippings, correspondence, and report, 1936-37 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  - New York State Association of Trial Lawyers: correspondence, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  - New York State Citizens Information Service: minutes, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  - New York Teachers Guild: program, 1958 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - New York University
    - General: printed material, 1950, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Alumni Association: agendas, correspondence, lists, printed material, and programs, 1959-71, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - School of Law: correspondence and lists, 1959-71 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - New York Urban League: correspondence (includes Jackie Robinson), 1966-71 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - New Yorkers for Abortion Law Repeal: correspondence, newsletters, and transcripts, 1970-71 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity: correspondence, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Parents Association: printed material, 1959-60 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Petitions: letters, printed material, 1957-66, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Phi Beta Kappa: correspondence, invitations, and newsletters, 1954-71 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Pioneer Youth of America: correspondence, 1949, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Planned Parenthood: correspondence, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Practicing Law Institute: correspondence, 1964-65 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Project Find
    - Overview: budget, bylaws, newspaper clippings, and publicity, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1967-71 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Programs: documents, lists, proposals, and reports, 1967-71, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Proportional Representation Campaign Committee: correspondence, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Public Affairs Committee: minutes, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - A. Philip Randolph Institute: clippings, correspondence, and program, 1969-70 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor Organizations: correspondence and programs, 1964-65 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - SANE: correspondence (includes Benjamin Spock), leaflets, 1965-66 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Sheppard Youth Center, correspondence, 1971 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Smith College, [see also SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS]
    - General: convocation and inauguration programs, 1949, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 22)
    - Alumnae Association: correspondence, 1967-69 (Box 50, Folder 23)
    - Alumnae College: programs, 1942-56 (Box 50, Folder 24)
    - Club of New York: correspondence, invitation, and program, 1953-64 (Box 50, Folder 25)
    - Friends of the Library: invitation and Annual Report, 1959-64 (Box 50, Folder 26)
    - Sophia Smith Collection: correspondence and printed material, 1959-66 (Box 50, Folder 27)
  - Snag Club: agendas and correspondence, 1963-68 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  - Society for Ethical Culture: correspondence, minutes, and programs, 1965-69 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  - Soroptimists Club: report, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  - Students for Democratic Reform at New York University: correspondence and newsletter, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  - Taxpayers Campaign for Urban Priorities: correspondence (includes Bella Abzug), 1969 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Testimonial Dinners: correspondence (includes Norman Thomas, Bayard Rustin, and A. Philip Randolph), programs, and publicity, 1950-71, [see also SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS] (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Town Hall Club: invitation, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Tresca, Carlo Memorial Committee: pamphlet and clipping, 1945-49 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Turn Toward Peace: correspondence, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Twenty-Second and Twenty-first Streets Community Council: agenda, correspondence, and petition, 1960-61, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Twenty-Third Street Association, [SEE Lower West Side Community Development Activities] (Box 51)
  - Union for Democratic Action: program, 1945 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - United Nations
    - General: newspaper clippings, and printed material, 1952, 1967, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - General Assembly
      - Lists, publicity, reports, and resolutions, 1946-47 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Trusteeship Council: memoranda, questionnaire, and resolutions, 1947, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Economic and Social Council
      - Administration
        - Calendars, 1948-49 (Box 51, Folder 11)
        - Document indexes, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 12)
        - Membership lists, 1946-49 (Box 51, Folder 13)
        - Non-governmental organizations: communications and recommendations, 1946-49 (Box 51, Folder 14)
        - Publications
          - Economic and Social Council Journal, 1946 (Box 51, Folder 15)
          - Official records, 1947-48 (Box 51, Folder 16)
        - Record summaries, 1948-49 (Box 51, Folder 17-18)
        - Reports, 1947-49 (Box 52, Folder 1)
        - Resolutions
          - Adoptions, 1947-49 (Box 52, Folder 2)
          - Drafts, 1947-49 (Box 52, Folder 3)
        - Rules and procedures, 1946-49 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Ad Hoc Committee on the Organization and Operation of the Economic and Social Council: summary record and recommendations, 1951 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Commission on Human Rights
        - General: fact sheet, 1947 (Box 52, Folder 6)
        - Drafting Committee for International Declaration of Human Rights: drafts, minutes, and reports, 1948-50 (Box 52, Folder 7)
        - Reports, 1946-47 (Box 52, Folder 8)
        - Session records
          - 7th session in Palais des nations, Geneva: agendas, amendments, resolutions, and summaries, 1948 (Box 52, Folder 9-10)
          - 5th session at Lake Success, NY: agendas, amendments, resolutions, and summaries, 1949 (Box 52, Folder 11)
        - Subcommission on the Prevention of Discrimination and Protection of Minorities: agendas, memoranda, minutes, proposals, reports, and resolutions, 1949-50 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Commission on International Social Policy: fact sheet, position paper, 1948-49 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Commission on the Status of Women, [see also SERIES VIII. PHOTOGRAPHS; SERIES IX. AUDIOVISUAL MATERIAL; and SERIES X. OVERSIZE MATERIAL]
        - General: overviews and newspaper clippings, 1946-52, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 1)
        - Planning
          - Conference on the UN and the Special Interests of Women: correspondence, interview transcripts, lists, memoranda, publicity, and reports, 1945-47 (Box 53, Folder 2)
          - Subcommission on the Status of Women: agendas, correspondence, memoranda, minutes, proposals, reports, and resolutions, 1946-48 (Box 53, Folder 3)
          - Working Group Concerned with the Commission on the Status of Women: agendas, memoranda, proposals, and reports, 1946-47 (Box 53, Folder 4)
          - Founding documents: charts, proposals, reports, and resolutions, 1946-48, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 5)
        - Administration
          - Agendas, 1946-48, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 6)
          - Membership: biographies, lists, and proposals for new members, 1946-50, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 7)
          - Memoranda, 1947-49 (Box 53, Folder 8)
          - Non-governmental organizations (Box 53)
            - Relations: correspondence, lists, memoranda, notes, and resolutions, 1946-49, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 9)
            - Proposals, 1947, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 10)
            - Communications, 1946-50 (Box 53, Folder 11)
            - Networking: correspondence adn lists, 1947-48, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 12)
          - Publicity
            - Newsletters, 1961-65 (Box 53, Folder 13)
            - Press releases and statements, 1946-50 (Box 54, Folder 1)
            - Radio broadcast transcripts, 1949, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 2)
          - Recommendations, 1949 (Box 54, Folder 3)
          - Reports and resolutions, 1948-50, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 4-5)
          - Session records
            - First session, Lake Success, NY: summary reports of meetings 1-19, 1947 (Box 54, Folder 6)
            - Second session, Lake Success, NY:
              - Preparation, 1947 (Box 54, Folder 7)
              - Summary reports of meetings 1-12, 1948 (Box 54, Folder 8)
            - Third session, Beirut, Lebanon
              - Planning material: minutes, and proposals, 1948-49 (Box 55, Folder 1)
              - Preparation, 1949 (Box 55, Folder 2)
              - Summary reports for meetings 39-63, 1949 (Box 55, Folder 3-4)
              - Post-mortem publicity, 1949 (Box 55, Folder 5)
          - State Department telegraphic summaries, 1947-48 (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
          - Miscellaneous: invitation and notes, 1951, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 8)
        - Correspondence
          - General
            - 1945-46 (Box 55, Folder 9-11)
            - 1947-Mar 1948 (Box 56, Folder 1-13)
            - Apr 1948-49 (Box 57, Folder 1-15)
            - 1950-53 (Box 58, Folder 1)
          - Individuals, [see also League of Nations correspondence]
            - Dean Acheson, 1948-49 (Box 58, Folder 2)
            - Florence Allen, 1947 (Box 58, Folder 3)
            - Margery Corbett Ashby, 1947-49 (Box 58, Folder 4)
            - Mary McLeod Bethune, 1947-48 (Box 58, Folder 5)
            - Carrie Chapman Catt, 1946-47 (Box 58, Folder 6)
            - Mary (Molly) Dewson, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 7)
            - India Edwards, 1948 (Box 58, Folder 8)
            - Katherine Ellickson, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 9)
            - Felix Frankfurter, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 10)
            - Emmy Freundlich, 1947-48 (Box 58, Folder 11)
            - Hubert Humphrey, 1948 (Box 58, Folder 12)
            - Fiorello LaGuardia, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 13)
            - Frieda Miller, 1945-49 (Box 58, Folder 14)
            - Alva Myrdal, 1949 (Box 58, Folder 15)
            - Pauline Newman, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 16)
            - Eleanor Roosevelt, 1946 (Box 58, Folder 17)
            - Dean Rusk, 1948-49 (Box 58, Folder 18)
            - Rose Schneiderman, 1946-49 (Box 58, Folder 19)
            - Anna Lord Strauss, 1947-49 (Box 58, Folder 20)
            - Ruth Woodsmall, 1948-49 (Box 58, Folder 21)
        - Addresses and articles by Kenyon, [see also SERIES VI ARTICLES AND ADDRESSES] (Box 59, Folder 1)
        - Subjects (and issues)
          - Education: resolutions and statements, 1948-49, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 2)
          - Enfranchisement: resolutions and printed material, 1947-48 (Box 59, Folder 3)
          - German women: memoranda and speech by E. Roosevelt, 1947-49 (Box 59, Folder 4)
          - Greek women: typescripts, 1948-49 (Box 59, Folder 5)
          - Housing: proposals and resolutions, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 6)
          - International Congress of Women [see Women's International Democratic Federation below] (Box 59)
          - Legal status: correspondence and typescripts, 1946-49, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 7)
          - Marriage: reports and resolutions, 1948-50 (Box 59, Folder 8)
          - Nationality: notes, proposals, reports, and resolutions: 1947-50, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 9-10)
          - Political rights: proposals, reports, and resolutions, 1946-50 (Box 59, Folder 11)
          - Prostitution: legal documents, printed material, and resolutions, 1947-48 (Box 59, Folder 12)
          - Public service and office-holding: memoranda, reports, and resolutions, 1948-51 (Box 59, Folder 13)
          - Public opinion: resolutions and reports, 1948 (Box 59, Folder 14)
          - Questionnaire on the Legal Status and Treatment of Women
            - Discussion and planning: memoranda, notes, proposals, 1947-49, n.d. (Box 59, Folder 15)
            - Drafts
              - Part I, 1946-49 (Box 59, Folder 16)
              - Part II, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 17)
              - Part III, 1949 (Box 59, Folder 18)
              - Entire document, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 1)
            - Replies, 1947, 1949 (Box 60, Folder 2)
            - Resolutions and Reports, 1948, n.d. (Box 60, Folder 3)
          - Religion: resolution, 1948 (Box 60, Folder 4)
          - Social Policy in Non-Metropolitan Territories: printed material, 1947 (Box 60, Folder 5)
          - Soviet women: newspaper clippings, reports, and statements, 1948-49 (Box 60, Folder 6)
          - Women's International Democratic Federation: correspondence and statements, 1945-47 (Box 60, Folder 7)
          - Working women: notes, printed matter, programs, resolutions and reports, 1946-50 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - United Nations International School: correspondence and printed material, 1952, 1964 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - United Negro College Fund: programs, 1951, 1955-56 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - United Neighborhood Houses: invitation and program, 1951-1954 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - University of Texas--Phi Beta Kappa Investigation: bulletin and report, 1946 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - USO of New York City: correspondence, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Village Independent Democrats: correspondence, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Women's Forum: program, 1949 (Box 61, Folder 7)